[
    {
        "question": "What is the full form of Ajax?",
        "choices": [
            "Asynchronous JavaScript And XML",
            "Asynchronous jQuery And XML",
            "Asynchronous JavaScript And XHTML",
            "Asynchronous jQuery And XHTML"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0
    },
     {
        "question": "_______ JavaScript is also called server-side JavaScript",
        "choices": [
            " Microsoft",
            "Navigator",
            "LiveWire",
            "All the above"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "In AJAX you can ",
        "choices": [
            "Update a web page without reloading the page",
            "Receive data from a server - after the page has loaded",
            "Send data to a server - in the background",
            "All of the above"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the object used for AJAX request?",
        "choices": [
            "HttpRequest",
            "xmlRequest",
            "XMLHTTPRequest",
            "Request"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Ajax is aâ€¦",
        "choices": [
            "Programing Language",
            "Technology",
            "OOPs concepts",
            "Options B and C"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Implementing AJAX in our websites we can make our web pages ________ ?",
        "choices": [
            "More Dynamic",
            "More interactive and faster ",
            "More Responsive",
            "Easy to connect web page with server"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "AJAX allows web page to dynamically",
        "choices": [
            "Change content",
            "Reload at times",
            "Control other pages",
            "Connect to other addresses"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one of these technologies is NOT used in AJAX?",
        "choices": [
            "CSS",
            "DOM",
            "DHTML",
            "Flash"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "AJAX made popular by",
        "choices": [
            "Microsoft",
            "IBM",
            "Sun Microsystem",
            "Google"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "_____ JavaScript is also called client-side JavaScript",
        "choices": [
            "Microsoft",
            "Navigator",
            "LiveWire",
            "Native"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1
    }
]
